BGM
Here we go, UpCami, this time with Kirara Yonemura of Ochanomama and Hisaki Ebata of Chus Chus!
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
I'm Yonemura, and I've recently been taking a voice training course, which includes Pilates.
Voice training doesn't require a lot of body movement.
But my teacher taught me Pilates to strengthen my inner muscles and stretch my abdominal muscles to improve my singing voice.
But I don't usually do any muscle training.
I don't usually do any muscle training.
I don't do that.
I'd like to take this opportunity to work harder.
I certainly want to work hard too.
I went to Okinawa for the spring tour, and we had time for sightseeing the next day after the tour.
The next day, we had a sightseeing time, and we were divided into two groups, "a" and "b", and each group went to the group they wanted to go to.
The next day, we had time for sightseeing, and the people who wanted to go in groups were divided into two groups, "a" and "b", and they went to whichever group they wanted to go to.
It was so cold.
So, we all had to stand on the sofa cushions like this while we ate.
I heard they have this.
That's right.
We made an umbrella barrier, but it almost got blown away, but it was the first time in my life that I experienced that, so I thought it was a lot of fun to barbecue in the storm.
It's true that the rain made it more memorable, and I'll never forget it.
I'm glad you guys had a good time touring Okinawa!
Now, let's start with this video!
The making of the Beyonce's Go City Go music video shoot!
The Beyonce's latest single "Go City Go" was released on May 29th!
Here's a sneak peek at the making of the music video for Beyonc's newest single, "Go City Go" released on May 29th!
Can you please let the sound out of your head once?
Please do.
I'm going to take a rip.
I have so many things I really want to tell you!
Go! City Go!
City Go! City Go! City Go!
City Go! City Go! City Go! The City City
Go! City Go! City Go! City Go!
Music video shooting for "Go! City Go!
We are shooting the music video in two days.
We filmed on location with everyone outside. We've been filming together outside a little bit, like on location.
I think we'll be dancing a lot in the studio today.
I'm going to do my best to look cute!
After all, the costumes are so cute! Look at them!
They're all wearing the same outfit.
It's very unusual for BEYOND!
And the tie is like this.
It's like a bullet train? It's like a bullet train motif.
I love that part too, so please check it out!
I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!
If it's with you, I still love you
Tokaido: Back on the Tokaido, running through now.
I can't wait, just like me.
I have so many things I want to tell you
There's a song for you
Rise on stage with the high
Yoi, sound!
Here's a phrase, Candyback, Garagolo yuku haru, Shin-Osaka, Chi yori
Wow!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Good night.
Thank you for watching.
Go! Citi!
Citi!
Go! Citi! Go! Citi!
Go! Citi! Go! Citi! Go!
Go! Citi! Go! Citi! Go! Citi!
A noisy man
The Sound of Shoes Diving Into Love
Place Efficiency
knows no lie
When it's light
The song is a collaboration with JR Tokai
the name of the Tokaido Shinkansen station appears in the lyrics The name of the Tokaido Shinkansen station appears in the lyrics
I can remember the name of the station if I listen to this.
I can remember the station names after listening to this!
It's fun!
Also, the costumes and
It's a little bit like an image
Like a conductor.
Tokaido Shinkansen trains are blue, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Maybe that's why it's blue.
That set of bullet trains is blue, too, right?
That's right.
It's full of train elements.
And the choreography.
Yes, yes, yes.
Shinkansen.
It's very fast.
Yes, yes, yes.
Round and round and round
We are very fast too, aren't we?
Yes, we are.
The choreography is fast, too.
I think you can feel the new concept
I think you can feel the new concept.
I have so many things I want to tell you
I think the song is what makes it exciting
This work is called GO!
CITY GO!" was filmed over a two-day period.
This time, there were many choreographies based on the theme of Shinkansen (bullet train).
There were many Japanese-style dances with beautifully aligned hands.
We are all dancing with a lot of consciousness.
Please take a look at the expressions of the members and how they use their hands.
and how they use their hands.
Thank you for watching!
The color of the members
Oisui old water
Aeon very good partner
I'm glad you're here.
I'm so happy!
I wonder if there is such a stylish bullet train
It's so cool!
It looks like you can't fold down the seats.
You can't fold down the seat.
Yes, thank you very much.
That's all for now, ladies and gentlemen of Japan!
Thank you for your hard work!
This time we shot the music video over two days.
On the first day, we filmed us in our natural state.
Today, we wore uniforms, like a conductor's uniform, and danced.
We also shot on a set that looked like a bullet train.
I think it's a rare opportunity to see a different side of us in one music video.
I think it's a very rare video that allows you to see a different side of us in one music video.
I hope you will watch it and enjoy the various eye contacts and the cute interactions between this girl and that girl.
I hope you'll watch it and find all kinds of eye contact, or cute interactions between this girl and that girl...
I hope you'll watch it and find all kinds of eye contact and cute interactions between this girl and that girl, and all kinds of other wonderful things.
Please watch a lot!
It was so cute!
It was a collaboration with the Tokaido Shinkansen.
The costumes and the set really looked like a bullet train.
And the choreography was also like this.
I thought it was really fun to watch.
And when you look behind the scenes of the dance shots, it's really fun to see how the dancers are all dancing together.
I was really impressed by the way the dancers were all dancing together.
I learned a lot from this video alone.
Yes, that's right.
It's called "Go City Go".
At the beginning of the song and many other places
Go City Go" is so catchy.
I thought it was wonderful that it stuck in my head even if I heard it only once.
Also, there are a lot of solo connections.
There are a lot of connections with each other.
I thought it was really fun to hear each member's voice.
I thought it was really fun to hear each member's voice.I thought it was a lot of fun!
This song is a collaboration between JR Tokai and BEYOND.
CITY GO! Campaign is now underway.
CITY GO! Campaign is currently underway.
CITY GO! Campaign website for more details.
CITY GO! Music Video Filming Making of "BEYOND GO!
Thank you for watching!
CITY GO! NOW ON SAIL!
Thank you for everything! I'll be rooting for you too!
Next is here. Dance lecture by Natsume Nakayama and Nanami Kubota.
In this corner, they will lecture the choreography of the choruses of songs other than the singles.
Please take a look then.
With Nanami Kubota of Ocha no Oma,
This is Natsume Nakayama from Ocha-no-Oma.
In this corner, we would like to give you a lecture on the choreography of the choruses of our non-single songs.
Yay!
So, what song will you lecture today?
Today,
Oh!
I would like to lecture the chorus of "Bare Skin on a Tropical Night.
Yay!
This song is a part of our second single,
Today, I would like to teach you the chorus of "Bare Skin on a Tropical Night.
Okay, so first of all, I would like to show you how to dance as a model.
Yes, please.
Please do it.
Subtitle by Miku Hatsune
No, I have to be the star.
Now, now, now...
I miss you.
Okay, now then, I'd like to give you a lecture on the chorus.
first of all, you do "shimmer, shimmer, shimmer" with your right hand from left to right, and then you lower your hips together.
You can touch it.
And then you're going to touch it, and then you're going to thrust it forward, and then you're going to connect it with your hand like this, and then you're going to burn it like this.
23 c or 4 times... let's do it one time...Let's do 23 c or 4 times, then let's try one more time.
I'll touch the half-turned tire, and then we'll move on to the next one, which is in a different direction.
I'll go on the left, you go on the left, and I'll go on the right.
I'll go on the right, and you slide your hand next to your face, either to the left or to the right.
Right?
I whisper and wave my body, and then I have them put their hands on their head like, "Oh, my God, what should I do?
If you can, bend your hips or legs a little bit to make it look better.
Then let's do it one more time.
One, two, three, four...
You can touch her bare skin, but don't whisper to her
He says you're beautiful
Then we'll do the right leg and the right hand.
Then we'll go back to the front.
Now, the right foot and the right hand... and then back to the front.
open your heel outward, then back inward, open outward and back in.
Okay, let's try it. One, two, three, four.
That's good. That's good.
Where was I?
Hey, the city's glistening.
Here's the same hand as before.
Hey, Tire.
Okay, four times to the lyrics and the music.
One, two, three, four.
Yes, sir.
And then...
Raise your right foot in the leading role.
Yes, sir.
Feet slightly inward.
Bring your right foot and your right hand up.
When the hand goes up, it should be right in front of you.
Yes, sir.
And when you bring it down...
When you bring it down, you stab it like this, from here to here.
Just like Burn's hand.
If you don't want to be the star, you put your palm forward.
If you remember Kubo and Nanami, you stab them now.
Now, now, now, now.Now, now, now.
&&& will be all of them.
Okay.
I'll do the solo part, so I'll do it like this.
I'll do "now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now...
If you have time, you can learn Kubo and Nanami's choreography.
If you have more time, you can learn Kubo and Nanami's moves, and if it's too difficult, you can point toward Kubo and Nanami.
If it's too difficult for you, just point toward Kubo and Nanami.
And that's the end of the chorus.
So you've got my drift, I guess I'll just have to sing it out loud.
I'm going to sing it with my mouth...
I'm beautiful, I'm beautiful, I'm beautiful, I'm beautiful, I'm beautiful, I'm beautiful, I'm beautiful...
I have to be the star, now, now, now, now, now, now, now...
Now let's get you dancing with us.
Hey, the town's glitzy, yeah, the tires are glitzy
You've got to be the star of the show
now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now...
I miss you.
How was everyone?
Thank you very much.
The point of this song is the rhythm of the song,
There are tires and other detailed rhythms,
Also, when the lyrics say "Whisper it to me," it's like you're whispering with your hand over your mouth,
The choreography fits the meaning of the song very well,
I think it will be easier to dance if everyone thinks about that.
I think this song is relatively easy among the songs of Ocha-no-Obaba,
I think it is easy for everyone to imitate,
I would be very happy if you could dance to it at live performances.
That's all for now, Natsume Nakayama and Nanami Kubota,
Natsume Nakayama and Nanami Kubota.
Bye bye.
So, here is the dance lecture of "Bare Skin is a Tropical Night.
Well, I have been dancing "Bare Skin is a Tropical Night" for a long time,
I have been dancing for a long time, but I am so used to it that I have never had a chance to check the choreography again,
I have never had a chance to check the choreography again, so watching this video made me realize that, yes, that part was indeed correct,
I would like to practice by watching this dance lecture video.
Yes, that's right.
I would like to practice the right to left, right to left with my right hand, and so on,I don't know how to do it, but I can't tell if I'm doing it right or left or right or left or right,
I'm the kind of person who doesn't understand right and left even when they're reversed.
I understand.
Do you understand? So it was very easy for me to understand what you were saying,
I think I was able to remember a little bit of it, so if there is an opportunity to see you on stage or something, I would like to dance with you,
If I have a chance to see you on stage or something, I would like to dance with you.
I want to see it. I want to see Ema-chan's bare skin.
I feel like singing.
Really?
At a birthday event or something.
I'll be waiting for it.
Yes, I am.
That's all for now, this is a dance lecture by Natsume Nakayama and Nanami Kubota.
I'm sure something good will happen.
Starry sky Somewhere in the starry sky
We don't have a pattern like this very often.
Let's start from the chorus of the first number.
Okay, let's see...
Okay. Bye.
Fee, fee.
Let's start here.
Let's finish up.
Okay.
Okay. - Okay.
me
Oh, oh, oh, I have a feeling I'm going to miss you
Some frame or year was a light will be my way
ah ah ah ah ah ah
I've already got the feeling, I just need to get the pitch just right.
Let's see if I understand
ah ah ah, I only have a dazzling premonition now
In the summer
It's been a year
It's going to be my way
ok, so it's for the juniors too
be my path.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
hope-colored waves are always flowing in a fickle shipIt's always the waves of hope that wash over the frayed ship
I can go anywhere
me
me me me
And the ass bar
Brians of MEMORIES
I'd better watch it in Clément.
Yes, ma'am.
Brians of MEMORIES
The light will be my path
I feel it
Sailing the fickle ship
Waves of ever hopeful colors
I can go anywhere I want to go
Briance of Memories
Brians of Memories
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Let's do AB Melody.
Thank you for watching.
I wonder if I dropped it. We had an appointment.
I don't know, I feel like it.
It's so cool. It's really good.
I like what you just did. Why are you so surprised?
I think it's hard to get into the starry sky at the beginning, but once you get it right here, the rest of the song is totally good.
If you put too much force into it, it will be hard to get it out, and if you relax too much, it will be hard to get in.
I think it's a very difficult entrance, but once you get it right here, the rest is totally fine.
I wonder if I dropped it somewhere in the starry sky.
We had a promise, didn't we?
I have a feeling we did.
OK, good.
Okay, let's continue.
We had a promise, didn't we?
I think so, but...Though it feels like it
Who am I going to meet?
And what awaits me there
I don't know
All the way to today
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's how I feel
All the way to today.
And...
That's right.
I wonder what it's been all this time.
I hear you've been working hard.
I think that's good.
I've been trying to imagine the words as if they were connected.
I've been singing this song for a long time.
I see.
Okay, let's go.
I have a feeling that's what I'm going to do.
Who am I going to meet?
What's waiting for me there
I don't know who I'm going to see
I'm going to meet my love
And then, number one, Shirin Way
I'll leave this here for a moment
For a new morning, my heart is empty
Yeah!
Put this down already
I've got a tailwind in my sails.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
All the way to today
Because a new morning will make my heart feel full
I've got the wind in my sails
I'm having fun
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's what I'm talking about.
That's goodAll right.
Here's another bottle, just in case.
Yes, ma'am.
All the way to today.
Because a new morning, my heart's empty
I've got a tailwind in my sails
It's fun.
Okay, that's good, isn't it?
That's good, isn't it?
Okay, well, thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
And Jess, please give my best wishes to Jess Jess!
Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you very much!
Well then, thank you all for your hard work this time!
Thank you very much for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work today.
From now on, I will take care of Japan after this and send you on your way.
Today, I would like to introduce you to the events of Jess Jess.
I would like to introduce you to some of them.
First of all, I would like to thank you for your hard work.
I'm Akari Uemura from JuusJus!
So, I have finished my last recording as Juice Juice!
So, that's it.
I just recorded my solo song as my graduation song this time.
Well, even before coming here, I didn't feel like it was the last time.
I was relaxed as usual.
But I was struggling with the highs and lows of this song.
I was struggling with the highs and lows of this song during voice training, but as the sessions went on, I gradually got a better grasp of it.
I felt that I was able to grasp the highs and lows of this song in a way that only Taisei-san can, and I really enjoyed it.
I think we had a lot of fun recording the song today.
I think we had a lot of fun recording the song today, and I think that's half of the greatness of this song.
I think I had a lot of fun recording this song today, and I think it was a great experience.
I think that's my purpose from now on.
I felt that this is a challenge for the future, and I'm looking forward to seeing how it will turn out.
It was almost like a chat, but we talked about deciding on a rough theme for writing this song.
So, I proposed the origin of my name and the theme of the song, "What I'm doing now.
What I'm doing nowI wrote this song about the work I'm doing right now and how it shines through me.
I hope that everyone will think that I am singing about myself and I will do my best to deliver the song to as many people as possible after the recording is over.
I would like everyone to think that I am singing about myself, and I would like to do my best to sing the song so that I can deliver it to as many people as possible after the recording is over.
I really enjoyed the recording. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I listened to "Brilliance of Memories. I listened to the song "Brilliance of Memories," and at this point, only a few JuiceJuice members have heard this song.
Is that so? We haven't listened to the sound source yet, but I love this song so much that I listen to it every day,
The sounds in the background are so beautiful, and the beauty of the song is so sparkling that it seems to represent Mr. Kamimura.
Personally, I like the second part where the melody changes a little bit.
Also, the last lyric of the song is "Whenever you get lost, you see, I'm guiding you.
It's really true, when one of the members of JuiceJuice is a little bit troubled
Mr. Uemura is the one who guides us with his words when one of the members of JuiceJuice is a little bit troubled.
This song really expresses Uemura-san so well.
I really want to listen to it all the time.
I was very happy to see the recording of this song.
This recording was the first time I heard this song.
As Eva said earlier, the music is beautiful, and so are the lyrics.
The lyrics of the song really fit you, Kamimura-san.
But the recording session was so cute.
The gap between the two was also very appealing, and it was a very enjoyable time.
That's all for Brilliance of Memories - Akari Uemura's vocal recording.
Thank you for watching!
I know you're working hard.
Kirara Yonemura and Kisaki Ebata have been presenting this episode of Apkami.
It's time for us to say goodbye. We've seen many different videos this time, but the one that left a personal impression on me, Ebata, was...
I was so surprised that there are only a few days left until Uemura-san's graduation performance.
It's amazing to see how little time is left until Uemura-san's graduation performance, but I'm so happy to see her getting more beautiful and more beautiful.
I'm so happy to see her getting more and more beautiful, and I'm sure the Budokan concert will be the best memory for me.
Watching the video
I'm also very sad to see you graduate, even though I haven't been as active as you, Eva.
I'm not as active as you, Eva, but I'm feeling very sad, so I think you must be sad too.
I'm also looking forward to the Budokan concert.
The scene that left the biggest impression on me was the making of the music video by BEYOND.
I think it's different to watch a music video after seeing the making of it.
I'm looking forward to seeing the music video again when I get back home.
I would like to watch the music video again when I go home.
In apkami, we are going to show you the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.We will take you behind the scenes of various artists' productions.
We'll introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see, so please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time, our up-cam partners are Kirara Yonemura of Ocha no Omame
and Ebata Kisaki of Chus Chus!
Good bye.
Next time on Upokami!
The making of Angulum Revitalization One Shot Music Video Shooting
and
the recording of "Fionn's High to Diamond" will be released!
Enjoy!
Thank you for watching!